STEPHANIE HANSON

Marketing Project Manager at Ad-orama

+1-483-603-8295 @ elonmusk@fakemail.com @ linkedin.com/in/stephanie.hanson Phoenix, AZ

SUMMARY

Marketing project manager with 11 years of experience as both an in-house and agency marketer. Well-acquainted with developing project timelines and roadmaps that have led to an increase in revenue as high as \$4.5M. Built relationships with over +50 enterprise clients in my career, with a 90% conversion rate.

EDUCATION

B.A. Marketing & PR

University of Phoenix

2007 - 2011

GPA **3.8** / 4.0

EXPERIENCE

Marketing Project Manager

Ad-orama

🗎 2019 - Ongoing 👂 Phoenix, AZ

Ad-orama is a full service advertising agency. We provide insightful strategic planning and comprehensive client service, relentless creative work and effective digital communication, flawless BTL and film-production services.

- · Increased the team's productivity by 20% after implementing Prince2
- Planned and managed up to 10 sustainable decommission projects at any given time with budgets ranging from \$10,000 – \$500,000
- · Built over 20 healthy relationships with returning clients
- Crafted and orchestrated the digital strategy and project roadmap for Coca-Cola's 2020 Christmas Ads, which brought in \$4.5M in revenue in December for Coke

Senior Marketing Project Manager

Renner-Kub

Renner-Kub is an innovative technology leader in branded, community-powered banking products proven to drive profit and growth for community financial institutions.

- Established a team of 7 people covering all aspects of in-house marketing, cutting down costs with 20%
- Boosted revenue by 30% by implementing content & email marketing strategies from key analysis
- Developed and implemented SEM, resulting in a 25% increase in revenue from \$1.2M in 2017 to \$1.5M in 2018
- Developed and orchestrated an aggressive social media marketing campaign that resulted in a 40% increase in conversion rate

Content & Digital marketing Project Manager

Torphy

🛗 2012 - 2015 👂 Phoenix, AZ

Torphy is an IT consulting firm based in Phoenix and present in over 20 countries around the world, with over 4,000 consultants.

- Responsible for project worth of \$10M with a distributed team
- Conducted gap analysis of marketing project management maturity and established a 3 year road-map for success
- Collaborated with Product Management, Marketing and Agency to plan quarterly B2C campaigns, increasing Torphy's clients by 40%
- Increased engagement by 15% on Instagram and LinkedIn by uploading branded content and exploiting the platforms' algorithms

ACHIEVMENTS

Q

Most successful ad of 2020

Coke's 2020 social distancing inspired ad for the Christmas Holidays won 10 awards in different categories, including Ad of the Year



Industry Influencer

Regular speaker at industry conferences, starting conversations on my blog with 80,000 monthly readers

SKILLS

Marketing

SEO SEM Data-driven Marketing

Social Media Management

R KPI

Email Campagins Digital Stategy

Project Management

Prince2 Waterfall Product Roadmaps

Budgeting Scheduling QA

ProjectLink

STRENGTHS



Always retrospect and improve

I always make sure I reflect on my past actions and see where I can do better in the future.

0

Time Management

Comfortable with juggling up to 10 projects simultaneously and meeting the deadlines.

